callutheran.edu 2017-06-24

# Web Privacy Policy | Cal Lutheran

### Purpose

California Lutheran University (Cal Lutheran) is committed to respecting your privacy. Cal Lutheran does not share personal information gathered from its web servers. We do not collect information about you other than connection information automatically collected and stored when you visit our Web site. Unless you choose to provide that information to us via online forms, no personal identifiable information is stored on our servers. 

Cal Lutheran also complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which prohibits the release of education records without student permission. Although FERPA regulations apply only to Cal Lutheran students, the University is equally committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our website. 

### Information Gathered by Cal Lutheran

Non-personally identifiable information. When you browse through any website, certain information about you can be collected. We automatically collect and temporarily store the following information: 

  * the IP address of the computer;
  * the date and time of the visit;
  * the pages visited; and
  * the address of the website from which you came.

We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, no additional information is collected about you. This non-personally identifiable information helps in diagnosing any server problems, administering the site, identifying the most popular areas of the site, and determining the effectiveness of promotional activities. 

For the same purposes, this website uses "cookies" – that is, small text files placed on your computer's hard drive – to help determine the type of content and sites visited, the length of time spent on a particular site, and the usage of services offered via the site. 

Personally identifiable information. Cal Lutheran does not require you to provide personal information to visit our website. However, you may choose to provide us with personal information through an e-mail message, form, survey, event registration, etc. This information is used only to fulfill the stated purpose of your communication and/or participation. 

The university does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (defined herein as minors younger than thirteen years of age) without obtaining parental consent. Before submitting personal information, Cal Lutheran requests that all minors have their parents read this Privacy Policy. 

### Security and Accuracy of Confidential Information

The privacy of communication over the Internet cannot be guaranteed because the Internet is not a secure medium. Although Cal Lutheran employs security measures to protect our servers and communication, Cal Lutheran does not assume any responsibility for any harm, loss or damage incurred by sending of personal or confidential information over the Internet to Cal Lutheran. 

### E-commerce

Some websites within Cal Lutheran enable you to pay for products or services online with a credit card. Unless otherwise noted, these transactions are encrypted. It is University policy that confidential information you enter in the transaction is used only for the purposes described in that transaction, unless an additional use is specifically stated on that site. 

### Sharing of Information

Cal Lutheran does not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our online visitors to third parties except as required by law. 

### Copyright Infringement

Cal Lutheran complies with Title II of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). Please submit claims of copyright infringement for the Cal Lutheran domain, callutheran.edu, to [domainadmin@CalLutheran.edu](mailto:domainadmin@CalLutheran.edu). 

### Questions

If you have questions about this privacy statement or you believe that your personal information has been misused or released without your consent, please send an e-mail to [web@CalLutheran.edu](mailto:web@CalLutheran.edu).
